Medical card, admission paperwork. Now that we have your ID and receipt, we should be good to head home.
Hey, thanks again for this, Dad.
I'm not your father.
At least those kids should be safe for right now. Must be bad if they're having to hide Lu Guang.
I know. From what we saw of his wounds, they must be mixed up in something dangerous.
Good thing Dad can pass for Lu Guang. It gave him a reason to shave and get a haircut. Doesn't he look good?
He most certainly does. I'm a little jealous now.
Hey, you. This place is a hospital, not a morgue. So go die somewhere else.
You're hogging my seat. Huh? What are you, deaf? Hey, do you understand words, you old fart? Get lost.
Ah, why are you even here? I thought geezers like you all had bedtimes. You're too old to live the nightlife.
Hey, you didn't answer me.
All right, that's enough. Show some respect for your elders. Don't let him get to you, Dad.
Don't call me old. Or your dad.
Would you please, Cutter?
Come on. We're leaving anyway.
Yeah, you better leave. Stupid old people being here late at night.
Somebody help. Call the doctor. I was out having fun and now my stomach hurts real bad.
Come on, just make it stop already. It's killing me.
Ah! Holy hell, is that a snake?
That grown man has it coming.
Dad, would you please let it go now?
Wait, I almost forgot. Sorry.
I wanted to check in with Xiaoling before we left. I'll only be a moment.
That's odd. She's not answering her phone.
What? Do you think something happened to her?
She could be fine, but I'm getting a bad feeling. There might be trouble.
Should we go back to the ward and check on them?
Hmm. It looks like it's too late for that.
You see those men walking towards the building behind us?
They're practically reeking with murderous intent.
You're right. We have to hurry.
Hold on. I want to help them out as much as you do.
But remember what Xiaoling said. We can't let them see us.
But they need our help. There has to be a way.
Sorry we took Xiaoling. We had to pick up something on the way over.
I can't believe this is real.
What do you say they were? Triple what?
Xiaoling warriors!
More like the triple star geezers.
Go on. Do the thing.
Say, door of courage. Sweeping away the fear with a lightness.
I'm sorry.
You two in the back should leave.
We've got this.
Yeah. Sure.
Hey.
You sound like you're a bit too old to be playing hero.
So what? Is this supposed to be like a senior citizens club or something?
Isn't it late for you?
Why don't you go on home and get some rest?
You're trying not to get people killed, remember?
What kind of freak are you?
You nearly took his head off.
No, you probably don't want to, but you're going to need to hold back on them.
He's right, Dad.
They're nothing but three old loons wearing costumes.
Take them out!
We've tolerated your evil wrong enough!
For a beautiful world, we will stop you!
Cut the act.
Tell us what happened at the hospital.
I'm very sorry, sir.
But I've told you everything I can remember.
You haven't said anything!
Now quit giving us the runaround.
Tell me!
But it's true!
All I remember was a flash of white light.
Then I woke up and my whole body was screaming in pain.
I saw a light and then I was on the ground.
I'm pretty sure I was dead for a little bit.
Yeah, I saw the light.
It was something else, man.
I felt light enough to float up into the sky.
It's a paradise.
It was one of those out-of-body experiences.
And this happened because you were beaten half to death by a superhero?
Come on!
Yeah.
No.
Not just one guy.
It was the Triple Star Warriors.
They tore through us like we were nothing!
Well, this is going nowhere.
I guess they're tougher than we thought.
I'm telling you, it was like watching a pissed-off martial god just unload their wrath.
I'm glad you're okay.
Well, we had help.
We're fine.
How about you?
Feel safe?
Security's much better.
The police are patrolling all the time now.
At least three officers are watching me at all times.
They rotate sometimes, just to be safe.
Now it's a lot harder for the killer to take over anyone who's on guard duty.
I think Captain Xiao wanted to make sure that if someone gets possessed, the others can stop him.
A lot has happened in the past few days.
I'm exhausted.
I need a nap.
Rest.
But make sure your door's locked first.
You can't be too cautious right now.
Wait.
What if you end up getting possessed?
Then he'll be all along with the killer.
You better handcuff yourself to the bed.
Is it me or did Lu Guang seem off?
Well, after everything he's been through, I would be more worried if he acted normally.
You're right.
Guess we're all still on edge.
Captain?
What happened to you?
I was attacked outside of the hospital.
They caught me off guard.
What about Officer Chen?
Do you have any idea who it was that attacked you?
Was it the people who attacked Officer Chen?
Did they take Liu Min's phone?
I don't have answers.
I screwed up.
And now we're stuck.
All of this happened because of my plan.
No, Captain.
You were keeping us safe the best you could.
We're grateful for that.
Yeah.
And thanks for keeping our powers a secret.
I'll ask for a demotion.
I got my partner killed.
That's on me.
But for right now, I have a murderer to catch.
Let us help.
Officer Chen, Emma, and who knows how many others.
We can't let their deaths be in vain.
I've already said as much to the higher-ups.
Not sure what they'll say.
This is all highly unprecedented.
But that can wait.
First, we need answers.
And we know one man who might have them.
Where did you learn to interrogate like that?
Guess old pigs can learn new tricks.
Enough.
Captain, this one's a talker, all right.
Just nothing useful.
Did you push Officer Chen off the roof?
Who, me?
You think I pushed that well-trained policeman?
How flattered do you think I could do anything to him?
If you ask me, he did it himself.
Why would you assume suicide?
Huh?
We know you were on the roof.
Well, I was going up onto the roof to get some fresh air.
Then I heard it.
Sounded like a sissy was ugly crying about something.
They kept saying, I'm sorry, over and over.
I rushed to see if I could help, but I got there right as they jumped down.
I was so scared, I ran inside.
Such a tragedy.
What could possess him to do that?
Maybe he felt bad for taking something he shouldn't.
Enough!
You take that back!
Calm down, Detective.
Stress kills, you know.
I was just guessing.
But that anger?
It's almost like you've got something to hide.
Chen Bean was a good man.
No one's going to believe he was corrupt.
Really?
He probably shouldn't have taken all those bribes then.
Not the best career move.
Check his kitchen if you don't believe me.
Say one more word about him and you're dead!
Captain, it's not worth it for me!
You won't get away with this, asshole!
I'll prove he's innocent!
Yes, yes, I'm aware of that.
His death is connected to Liu Min's suicide.
Chen Bean's innocent.
Once I prove it, you'll know why the money was there.
Those two are special, but they need time, of course, I'm sure.
Yes, I understand.
It's not clear to me, either.
I'll update you if anything changes.
I appreciate all your support with this.
The higher-ups are holding off till the case is closed.
They suspended the stabbing case.
That's good.
So, um, Liu Guang asked me to bring this.
He wanted to be here, but there was an unexpected snack.
I swear I'll come right back.
It'll be fine.
Please.
Not on your life!
I'm not letting you traipse off so you can reopen your wound!
Now get back in bed!
You want your guts to fall out?
Um, on second thought, I should get back in bed.
Liu Guang needs to rest for now.
But you're here.
That's enough.
Mr. Xiao, what's next?
Is there a plan?
Huh.
What a coincidence.
My son's memorial is right next to your partner's.
Are you here to mourn or finally give us some answers as to what happened?
Our son died in your interrogation room, and you think that I'm going to buy some bull about him strangling himself?
How stupid do you think I am?
My son wasn't depressed or mentally ill in any way.
Maybe you can tell me why he's dead.
I'm sorry.
He was related to multiple cases.
None of which are closed yet.
Oh, really?
Tell me about them.
Better yet, tell me why you killed him.
Please calm down.
Again, I'm sorry.
But he's gone.
Blaming the police won't change that.
You should know we caught your son breaking into their studio.
Yeah, that's true.
He was there too.
I don't care!
You can't prove it, and the dead can't deny.
Mr. Chen, didn't you say we could sue?
Yes.
Say the word.
Really?
When did you sell your soul, huh?
I still remember the cop you used to be.
So what happened?
Justice needs proof, not assumptions.
Don't do it!
We're police officers, not vigilantes!
You don't have to help me.
Just don't stop me from bringing that bastard to justice.
Huh.
You hear that?
If you can't find proof against my son, my lawyer will destroy you!
Cases take time.
I'm not waiting any longer.
With every delay, you spit on my son's grave!
I saw him attack someone with a knife.
I'll testify.
Oh, you will?
That's nonsense if I've ever heard it.
Liu Min was disabled.
He could barely move or do anything.
And you saw him attack someone?
That's just insane.
Mr. Chen, if they fake the evidence,
could we get more money out of it?
Why, yes, of course.
A lot more.
And they'd face charges.
Sounds like you better be careful.
Life must be so hard on a fixed salary.
Enough for a young officer to start taking bribes.
Shut up!
There's hardly room for baseless accusations!
But you can frame our child.
I was only talking about what I'd heard.
What's more, it's not baseless.
The secret is out.
The cops found the money that he hid.
Not another word!
You can't stop me.
I'll scream from the rooftops if I so choose.
What?
You want to fight?
Fine.
Go on and hit me, you prick!
Oh god, you all saw that, right?
He attacked first!
You're a policeman, so arrest that man!
He was literally asking for it, though.
You worthless rat!
Where do you get off?
Did your folks abandon you before they taught you respect?
Xin Xin!
Let him go!
Not yet.
Apologize.
Apologize for what?
The only attack I saw is on your face.
Way to go, landlady.
Hell yeah.
You're a landlady?
I want that violent maniac arrested right now!
You good?
Xin Xin, it's your call.
I can handcuff her if you want.
Let's meet up at the station.
Get your statement.
For this scratch, no.
You can't just walk away!
Enough!
Don't embarrass me.
Just let it go, okay?
Let's leave before you make things worse.
When did you take this?
It looks recent.
Oh, it's from when we got married.
What?
Uh, nothing.
Time sure flies.
I took that two years ago, and we still haven't had our ceremony.
Shouldn't Officer Chen's wife be here by now?
She should, but I couldn't find her.
Where is she?
It's getting late.
I'm worried.
What if something happened?
Uh, have I heard this before?
Look, she's here!
Huh?
Where are you going?
Let's go, huh?
I didn't know.
No, it's not.
Come on, what are you gonna do?
They're real.
Get in.
Let's not tell her.
Just let her open.
This is very.
This is again the folks!
You inconsiderate bastard, you lying selfish jerk!
Damn you! Look at you abandon me!
Over here!
You finally have some time off and you want to spend it here?
Why not? We can stay home when we get old.
And why? Why did you have to break every promise that you ever made me?
You said you would stay with me when we went shopping.
Or sit through a movie together from beginning time.
So many nights alone. You'd tell me you would come home soon, but you never did.
Hey, I assume you're still working?
Yeah, sorry. I'm almost done though.
I'm still waiting. Why haven't you come home yet?
Please don't force our daughter to grow up without ever having a chance to meet her father.
It just doesn't fit her. You know that.
It's too late for you to make up for the past.
But there's one last promise that I need from you.
You owe me.
Promise that you'll pay me back in our next life.
Okay?
It's done, my lady.
What?
How was it?
You all right?
There's been so much pain.
They didn't deserve this.
So, we should help them.
Yeah, we should.
Hey, stay right there.
Okay, sure thing.
What is this for?
I, Chenbin, am proposing to the love of my life.
In this moment, and every one after.
I'm sorry I can't always be there for the small things.
But I'm always leaving you alone.
Whether it's when we're shopping, or halfway through watching a movie.
And thank you for forgiving me, even during the times that I don't deserve it.
I swear, with all my heart, to love and protect you,
not just for the rest of this life, but the next and the next.
So, will you marry me?
Well, duh.
I already said yes, right?
But one proposal doesn't guarantee I'll say yes in my next life.
It's not that easy.
Then again, if you keep making me fall in love with you, I'll have to.
Wait!
Please!